A Finding Aid to the Sidney Simon Papers, circa 1917-2002, bulk 1940-1997, in the Archives of American Art AAA.simosidn
Archives of American Art
- Photographs, circa 1917-1997; Series 9; 3 Linear feet Boxes 5-10
  This series is arranged as two subseries.
  9.1: Photographs of People and Artwork, circa 1930-1996
  9.2: Photograph Albums, circa 1917-1997
  - People and Artwork, circa 1930-1996; 9.1
    - Sidney Simon, 1942-1996 (Box 5, Folder 17-19)
    - Sidney Simon and Family Members, circa 1956-1990 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Sidney Simon with Colleagues and Friends, circa 1968-1996 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - "Artwork by Sidney Simon, prior to 1938-1940", circa 1930-1937 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Photographs of Sculptures and Mobile, circa 1930-1937 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Scattered Photographs of Artwork, circa 1963-1981 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Oversized Photographs of Sidney Simon from Box 5, Folder 17, 1942-1964 (Box 9)
    - Oversized Photographs of Sculptures and Mobile from Box 5, Folder 23, 1957-1963 (Box 9)
  - Photograph Albums, circa 1917-1997; 9.2
    - Volume 1: Sidney Simon with Family, Friends, Colleagues, circa 1917-1940 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Volume 2: Sidney Simon with Family Members, circa 1918-1939 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Volume 3: "Rome, American Academy and Salzburg, Austria Seminar", 1969-1972 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Volume 4: "Paintings, Sculptures, and Murals", 1935-1941 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      Oversized material housed in Box 10
    - Volume 5: Sculptures - "Figurative Reliefs and Medals", 1951-1994 (Box 6, Folder 5-6)
    - Volume 6: Sculptures, "Portrait Heads, Busts, and Abstracts", 1952-1997 (Box 6, Folder 7-8)
    - Volume 7: "Mirror Series", 1953-1975 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Volume 8: Sculptures, "Black and White Photos", circa 1956-1990 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Volume 9: "Sculptures", 1958-1959 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Volume 10: "Mobiles", 1962 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Volume 11: Sculptures, "Extra Color Prints and Negatives", circa 1963-1990 (Box 6, Folder 13-14)
    - Volume 12: Sculptures, "Playground in Prospect Park", 1966 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Volume 13: "Sculpture", circa 1968-1973 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Volume 14: Sculptures, 1969-1973 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Volume 15: "Proposal for Sculpture for Jackson Memorial Hospital Ambulatory Care Center, University of Miami", 1979 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Volume 16: "Works for Architecture", 1958-1965 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Volume 17: "Two Works for Architecture", 1958-1965 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Volume 18: "Three Works for Architecture - Corpus, St. John, Downstate Medical Center, and Temple Beth Abraham", 1964-1966 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Volume 19: "West Point Jewish Chapel" (Disbound), 1984-1986 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Volume 20: "The Four Seasons Fountain, Worldwide Plaza" (Disbound), 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Volumes 21-22: "The Four Seasons Fountain, Worldwide Plaza", 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Volumes 23-24: "Sidney Simon: 40 Years of Work" (1995 August 18-October 30, Disbound) (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Volume 25: "Master Set of Color Prints for Commissions, Matisse's Mirror, Medals, Long Point Show, Competitions, and Terra Cotta", 1956-1994 (Box 8, Folder 2-3)
    - Oversized Volume 2: Sidney Simon with Family Members from Box 6, Folder 2, 1942-1996 (Box 9)
    - Oversized Volume 4: "Paintings, Sculptures, and Murals" from Box 6, Folder 4, 1935-1941 (Box 10)